crazyshirts.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy and Security - Crazy Shirts Official Site

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about information we may collect from or about you, what we do with that information and provide you with information about the opt-out process. 

Crazy Shirts sells men's, women's and children's casual apparel through its own catalogs, online web site (crazyshirts.com) and our corporately owned retail stores. Occasionally, we share our customer list with carefully screened companies whose products and services may interest you. We do not share customer telephone number or email address with outside companies. Our list is not available for telemarketing. 

If you do not wish to receive mailings from these other companies with whom we share customer lists, or do not wish to receive our catalogs, please contact us at 

Customer Service Department  
99-969 Iwaena Street  
Aiea, Hawaii 96701

Call us at 1-800-771-2720 or email us. 

**The Information We Collect**   
We collect transaction information and email addresses. We collect only the minimum information necessary to complete your order online; this is the same information required to complete telephone orders - name, billing and shipping address, telephone number, and payment information. We require customer email address for online orders so that we may notify you of your order status or merchandise return status. Additionally, if you opt-in, we may send you emails promoting our products, announcing special events and offering other special limited-time discounts, such as free shipping, that may be used by online customers. 

If you purchase from crazyshirts.com, your name and mailing address will be added to the Crazy Shirts print catalog mailing list and database. You may opt-out of receiving any catalogs or email promotional communication by clicking on the below link. 

We use third party advertising companies and marketing partners to serve ads on our behalf on the internet and in our web-based ads. We and our partners may use cookies, web beacons (also known as Gif tags, 1x1 pixels, action tags, etc) to deliver better, targeted marketing messages to consumers and to track certain information about how you navigate our website. We analyze and compile this information on an aggregated basis. This information may include information about your internet service provider, browser type, domain name, IP address, the web site that referred you to us, the web pages you request, the date and time of those requests, and entry and exit points. This information allows us to create a website that caters to the needs of our viewers and at the same time give them complete anonymity. 

Our website uses order forms for you to request information and buy Crazy Shirts products. We collect contact information (such as your email address), and demographic information (such as your zip code). We collect, but do not retain financial information (such as your account and credit card numbers). 

**Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alterations of the information under our control. All customer order information (like your e-mail address and credit card information) is transferred using HTTPS (secure http) and SSL (Secure Socket Layer). All data is encrypted by your browser and then decrypted by the Web server (our site), rendering the information unreadable. 

**Email Privacy Policy**   
Crazy Shirts does not sell or rent customers' email addresses to other companies. When you sign up for our email newsletter, we will send you announcements regarding new products, special events and promotions. Each email we send has a link enabling you to unsubscribe. Please note that if you request to be removed from our email updates database you will still receive email notifications and updates regarding any orders placed with crazyshirts.com 

**Remove or update my personal information**   
If you have registered for a crazyshirts.com account, we have provided you with a means to log into your account and edit your personal information including name, address, email address, phone number and account password to ensure its accuracy. 

If you signed up to receive email communications and wish to remove your address from our mailing list, you may use the Unsubscribe link provided in our e-mails, call us at 1-800-771-2720 or click [here](https://crazies.crazyshirts.com/pub/sf/ResponseForm?_ri_=X0Gzc2X%3DWQpglLjHJlTQGn5hbAkzc4dcLdWYeU4Aa0WpwunVXMtX%3DWQpglLjHJlTQGNzeSzcL4NzfGTlfoUerczdddfuHNn&_ei_=EkwRYXX_JFE95tjkB4_tS18). 

**We listen to you!**  
We read and respond to every message that is sent to us. A customer care representative will personally get back to you with in 24-48 hours. We do not retain any personal information from your email unless requested to do so.

**Policy Changes**  
If any changes are made to our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our web site. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. This policy was posted in April 2007. 

**Your Feedback**  
To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You may can email us or call us at at 1.800.771.2720.
